export const initialQuestionsAndAnswers = {
    graphicsAndVisual: [
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
    ],
    humanComputerInteraction: [
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
    ],
    infoAssurance:[
        { 
            id: 1, 
            question: "protect and defend information", 
            answer: "Information Assurance",
        },
        { 
            id: 2, 
            question: "info is not disclosed to person", 
            answer: "Confidentiality",
        },
        { 
            id: 3,
            question: "data cannot be created without authorization", 
            answer: "Integrity",
        },
        { 
            id: 4,
            question: "reliable access to data", 
            answer: "Availability",
        },
        { 
            id: 5,
            question: "to establish the validity of transmission", 
            answer: "Authentication",
        },
        { 
            id: 6,
            question: "sender == proof of delivery; recipient == proof of sender's identity", 
            answer: "Non-Repudiation",
        },
        { 
            id: 7,
            question: "data between processing", 
            answer: "Transmission",
        },
        { 
            id: 8,
            question: "data on persistent medium", 
            answer: "Storage",
        },
        { 
            id: 9,
            question: "data is in control", 
            answer: "Processing",
        },
        { 
            id: 10,
            question: "heart and soul; awareness, literacy, training...; must follow policy and practices; strength and vulnerability", 
            answer: "People",
        },
        { 
            id: 11,
            question: "system users; system administrations; software conventions; trust validation; countermeasure and vulnerability", 
            answer: "Policy and Practices",
        },
        { 
            id: 12,
            question: "crypto, hardware, software, network, platform", 
            answer: "Technology",
        },
        { 
            id: 13,
            question: "all parts change over time", 
            answer: "Time",
        },
        { 
            id: 14,
            question: "something that might happen ", 
            answer: "Threat",
        },
        { 
            id: 15,
            question: "where threat could compromise a system", 
            answer: "Vulnerability",
        },
        { 
            id: 16,
            question: "odds of system and consequences ", 
            answer: "Risk",
        },
        { 
            id: 17,
            question: "application of threat", 
            answer: "Attack",
        },
        { 
            id: 18,
            question: "successful attack", 
            answer: "Exploit",
        },
        { 
            id: 19,
            question: "what happened; fix to restore things", 
            answer: "Remediation",
        },
        { 
            id: 20,
            question: "to fix vulnerability", 
            answer: "Countermeasure",
        },
        { 
            id: 21,
            question: "heart of an information technology", 
            answer: "Access Control",
        },
        { 
            id: 22,
            question: "uniquely identify the users", 
            answer: "Identification",
        },
        { 
            id: 23,
            question: "permit the system to verify oneâ€™s identification credential", 
            answer: "Authentication",
        },
        { 
            id: 24,
            question: "predominant strategy to ensure confidentiality; to give people the least amount of access to a system", 
            answer: "Least Privilege",
        },
        { 
            id: 25,
            question: "maintains responsibility for the information within an information system; make the decisions about who uses the system", 
            answer: "Information Owner",
        },
        { 
            id: 26,
            question: "dictates that the information owner is the one who decides who gets to access the system", 
            answer: "Discretionary Access Control",
        },
        { 
            id: 27,
            question: "nondiscretionary access control; system decides who gains access to information; used in military and government systems", 
            answer: "Mandatory Access Control",
        },
        { 
            id: 28,
            question: "people or other systems that are granted a clearance to access an object", 
            answer: "Subjects",
        },
        { 
            id: 29,
            question: "being protected from use or access", 
            answer: "Objects",
        },
        { 
            id: 30,
            question: "binds objects to subjects; permits access to an object", 
            answer: "Labels",
        },
        { 
            id: 31,
            question: "assigning rights to the group for access control purposes; most appropriate where there is high turnover of employees", 
            answer: "Role-Based Access Control",
        },
        { 
            id: 32,
            question: "list of users who are given the privilege of access to a system; privileges includes CRUD", 
            answer: "Access Control Lists (ACL)",
        },
        { 
            id: 33,
            question: "granting access to new employees; include checking management approvals for grating access", 
            answer: "User Provisioning",
        },
        { 
            id: 34,
            question: "using passwords only for authentication", 
            answer: "Single factor authentication",
        },
        { 
            id: 35,
            question: "using more than one authentication mechanism", 
            answer: "Multifactor Authentication ",
        },
        { 
            id: 36,
            question: "user has a physical device that contains his credentials, protected by a personal identification number (PIN) or a password", 
            answer: "Two-Factor Authentication",
        },
        { 
            id: 37,
            question: "unique information (biometrics) related to the user is added for authentication", 
            answer: "Three-Factor Authentication",
        },
        { 
            id: 38,
            question: "measuring unique human characteristics as a way to confirm identity", 
            answer: "Biometric",
        },
        { 
            id: 39,
            question: "most common biometric in use", 
            answer: "Fingerprint",
        },
        { 
            id: 40,
            question: "measure of the likelihood that the biometric security system will incorrectly reject an access attempt by an authorized user", 
            answer: "False Rejection Rate (FRR)",
        },
        { 
            id: 41,
            question: "measure of the likelihood that the biometric security system will incorrectly accept an access attempt by an unauthorized user", 
            answer: "False Acceptance Rate (FAR)",
        },
        { 
            id: 42,
            question: "users have one password for all corporate and back-office systems and applications they need to perform their jobs", 
            answer: "Single Sign-On",
        },
        { 
            id: 43,
            question: "to provide authentication for client/server applications; works by assigning a unique key, called ticket, to each user", 
            answer: "Kerberos",
        },
        { 
            id: 44,
            question: "is a client/server protocol and software that enables remote access users to communicate with a central server", 
            answer: "Remote Access Dial-In User Service (RADIUS)",
        },
        { 
            id: 45,
            question: "a user connects to the Internet via his or her Internet Service Provider (ISP) and initiates a connection to the protected network", 
            answer: "Virtual Private Networks (VPN)",
        },

    ],
    introToArchi: [
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
    ],
    pldi: [
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
        { /* add key value pairs of question and answer */ },
    ],
}

export const randomChoicesInfoAssurance = initialQuestionsAndAnswers.infoAssurance.map(item => item.answer)
